This is AKB-0048's personal stage!
Uh-huh!
The Zero-Zero stage.
Amazing. There are so many people in the audience.
Are all these people fans?
Of course they are!
We're going to sing and dance for all these people.
Oh man! I'm feeling nervous!
I feel like I'm gonna die!
It's starting.
Hello! We'll be opening up for today's performance!
We're the 75th Generation Trainees!
75th Generation Trainees?
There's only two of them?
Please enjoy our song!
It's called Lemon's Edge!
The 75th Generation Trainees are known as the Unlucky Generation.
The Unlucky Generation?
There were a lot of dropouts.
Only two remain with us.
And those two haven't been able to become successors.
It's been two years.
Two years?!
But...
Yeah.
I think they're really good.
But they still don't.
Huh?
Doesn't this atmosphere seem a little strange to you guys?
Yeah!
Ah...
So now...
...
You can do it, Kanata!
Woody
Everybody.
1, 2, 3, 4.
1, 2, 3, 5.
I want you
I need you
I love you
Our great effort becomes a song
The tears we shed
Become stars
Thank you.
空の星だって何億光年の彼方 暗闇の先に輝くもの
希望について僕は語ろう 名もなき詩人のように熱く
君が涙に触れているなら 慰めよりもやがて
白の空を語ろうか
音楽
You're kidding!
Really?
Yeah, really.
Today's performing members were...
I get the feeling I'll never be able to stand on that stage!
This is the dressing room.
Sister!
You're amazing!
Sonata!
Sister!
Is she Sonata's older sister?
Oh, is that Kanda's younger sister?
You were really, really wonderful on stage, sister!
Sonata?
Sister!
You're heavy!
Subasa-san!
What is Sonata doing here?
What do you mean?
My sister is still underage.
She shouldn't be able to audition for this.
You're right.
But as you can see, she came to audition regardless.
I liked her determination.
But…
Yeah!
What she said!
I'm totally determined to be here!
With you, I'll…
Go home!
What?
Go home immediately!
You can't come here with us!
You don't have the right to decide that.
Uh…
Sonata is the only one who can decide what to do with her life.
They're from a different generation, but they're trainees just like you.
You will all be working together from now on.
These two are Kanada Shinanomi and Memori Kishira.
Hello, everyone!
I'm Memori.
It's nice to meet you.
Oh my!
I'm sorry!
It's nice to meet you!
Now, just try and relax everyone.
Let's all try to get along.
This is the Zero Zero Dorm where we all live.
Wow!
This is the cafeteria.
The food Chef Papa makes is superb.
Oh, are you girls joining us today?
I'm making a very special welcoming dinner tonight, so you all have that to look forward to.
Our lesson facilities have everything you need.
You can wash off your sweat in the bath, or eat snacks and chat.
Enjoy yourselves!
Everything is so beautiful!
It's so different from Katusha!
Oh, these sparkles!
This place is full of idle smell!
What do you mean, smell?
What?
You mean you don't know?
That appealing atmosphere left behind by fragrant and beautiful girls!
You have a strange taste.
What?
Let's see…
Makoto, Yuka, and Orine…
Oh, and Sonata…
This is your room.
What a cute room!
It's beautiful!
Your lessons will start tomorrow.
You should go to bed early after dinner, okay?
Okay!
Hey, sister…
Listen, I thought it might be fun if you started to…
Chiri-san, Nagisa-san, and Suzuko-san, you'll be staying in this room!
Okay!
Your luggage has arrived, so please make sure nothing is missing!
My new room…
My new self…
Everything starts here…
This is home…
Come on, everyone!
Give it your best!
You've gotta hustle!
Hustle!
Yeah!
Hustle…
How's your room?
It's simple and cute!
I wonder if the rooms are different at all…
Will you show us your room later, Nagisa?
Yeah!
Come visit me!
Uh…
Linda?
What are you doing?
Looking at these?
Photos of the previous generations?
They're all Center Nova's there.
Center Nova?
What's that?
Currently, AKB0048's Center changes depending on the song.
But previously, a member known as the Center Nova always stood at the center.
The last Center Nova was the 13th generation Achan.
But when Achan graduated, it was discontinued.
I remember 13th generation Achan.
She was at the concert we saw when we were kids.
She was so wonderful!
Before Achan was 5th generation Mi-chan.
Before her was 6th generation Yui-han.
Before her, 7th generation Yuko was the Center Nova.
That's amazing.
This group has a history.
But…
Why was the Center Nova position discontinued?
I know, right?
Uh…
Yuko-san!
Hiya!
I'll bring back the Center Nova position.
I'll never be satisfied with my current position.
Knowing there's something more gets you going!
Alright, ladies.
Up and at'em!
Let's get going!
Even though we're trainees, there's still more that lies ahead.
Even if we become successors, there's still more ahead.
When I imagine there's so much more, I get super excited!
Don't you?
Yes!
You know it!
No, no, no, no!
I'm not going home, dummy!
Enough already!
Wait, Kanata.
I can't believe you'd lie to get into Zero Zero.
You're a liar too!
Uh…
You said you'd become a member of Zero Zero 48, but you haven't even become a successor yet!
You liar!
Kanata…
I'm so tired…
You finally got to see your little sister again.
Don't you feel bad for her?
She doesn't understand anything.
Strenuous training.
The pain of never being rewarded no matter how hard you work.
I don't want her to experience such… frustration and misery.
It's okay!
See?
We're the 75th generation, the unlucky generation!
Maybe your little sister will be fortunate enough to pass the two of us quickly and become a successor on her own!
How can you joke about that?
It's already been two years.
Everyone from our generation quit already.
We practice desperately.
We even research the original members.
But…
They still won't let us become successors.
But to become a successor you need…
It's the nature of our souls, right?
I know that.
You can't receive an original member's name with just your personality and abilities.
But…
At this rate, I'm never going to get my revenge!
What?
Our father was the leader of an organization that fought oppression of entertainment.
I always sang because I wanted to see my father happy.
But…
In a battle against the DES…
I wanted to join Zero Zero to fight the DES who took my father from me.
I had no idea.
That's why…
I didn't want Sona to follow the same path I did.
This…
painful and dangerous path.
But you love singing, don't you?
Have you been listening?
I don't care anything about the music at all!
Your voice is beautiful. I like your singing.
Liking it isn't good enough.
I'll get revenge for my father!
In order to do that, I'll become a successor and be chosen to perform in dangerous locations so I can fight the DES.
Konata…
Wake up, Nagisa!
Nagisa?
I'm still tired.
You were up late watching Zero Zero PVs again, weren't you?
Your father will be angry.
Uh…
Zero Zero…
Oh, you're awake?
Did you dream of me?
I'm still tired.
You were up late watching Zero Zero PVs again, weren't you?
Your father will be angry.
Uh…
Zero Zero…
Oh, you're awake?
Did you dream too?
Ah…
Uh…
Good morning, Chihiri!
Hmm?
Oh, good morning.
We finally get dance lessons!
Farewell, strenuous combat training!
It's exciting, isn't it?
Seriously, those weren't lessons for an idol.
Yeah, yeah. I'm gonna dance like crazy!
You! You're offbeat!
Yes!
That's enough!
I'm gonna die!
Did you say something?
No! Nothing!
You, Shorty!
Did you learn that song before you came?
Don't call me Shorty!
I knew she couldn't do it.
I don't believe these pathetic girls.
No, no, no, no! You're all offbeat!
And the worst one of all is…
Kanara!
Huh?
Your dancing is completely lifeless today, young lady!
But…
These 77th generation girls have just started their lessons!
They're balls of potential!
How can this be the best you can do after two years of lessons?
How mean?
It's terrifying!
Let me see now…
What was your name?
Chievi?
Yes!
Come to the front, change positions with Kanara for the number.
Wait a minute!
Why are you letting someone who just joined do this?
I'm just considering the group's balance.
Besides, someone without any motivation is in no place to voice her opinion.
I…I can't do it…
What?
I haven't completely memorized the moves yet.
Please let me watch my seniors dance a bit longer.
I only just joined. I'm trying to learn this, but I don't know anything.
That's why I need my seniors to keep their act together.
Kanata! Kanata, wait!
I'm trying to learn this, but I don't know anything.
That's why I need my seniors to keep their act together.
Kanata!
Kanata, wait!
Hey, hey!
You were too harsh!
Seriously!
My sister's wonderful!
What?
She's more wonderful than anyone!
Her singing, her dancing…
But…
Starting today, your nickname's Meany!
Meany!
I've had enough.
Now that those two have disappeared, we're done for now.
Take a break.
Meany!
I kept the feeling there's going to be a great reaction.
You're right.
I don't think you should have said that.
Kanata-san's been working so hard, but she just…
I know.
What?
I can tell.
Her singing and dancing are probably both successor level.
She may even be better than them.
It must have taken a considerable amount of effort to get that good.
Cheery.
Mm-hmm.
There's such a thing as a person's original nature.
No matter how hard you work, there's a brilliance you can never obtain.
That's the glow of an idol.
Nagisa!
We're gonna go look for Kanata-san.
You!
Did you do something to Nagisa?
She didn't do anything.
Let's go.
I wonder what it is.
Singing.
Dancing.
All I wanna do is avenge my father.
Aka-be Od Miss!
I wonder what it is?
Singing.
Dancing.
All I want to do is avenge my father…
AKB, 0048 loves it too!
0!
New texture, new flavor!
Why do I always feel so frustrated?
Sometimes I can't dance
Even though I try
Music's just not in my heart
And so I cry
Sometimes I can't sing
But it's my everything
It must be that I'm worthless
Since I start to wonder
Why can everyone around me
Seem to do what I cannot so flawlessly
But tears are never truly in vain
Flowers only grow and blossom where there is rain
And I know that I'll be something truly beautiful
If you keep singing, I might
Remember your wishes can come true
But that first step can only be taken by you
And after all the rain
The sun will shine on you again
I'll start to like it
I'll end up liking singing
Well now tell me
What's wrong with liking it?
Liking things
It's always better to have more love
After all
AKB0048 are idols
Who go to see their audience
They're idols who sing out their love to everyone
Mimbori
Everyone has bad days
Sometimes we get caught up in the noise and the craze
But then I hear
The crowd start to cheer
And I know there is work to do
Who are we to deny an encore
After all the audience is begging for more
And I realize
This is what I've been looking for
My wishes
Kanata!
Sonata!
Amazing, Kanata!
You haven't become a successor yet
But you've already got a hardcore fan
Kanata!
Right, Kanata?
Come here, Sonata!
You girls too!
Huh?
Oh, okay!
夜の空輝く星は
何億光年の彼方
たとえ不快絶望が
無限の闇となっても
真実は伝わるんだ
時間の川に託した
その光のメッセージ
受け取るものは誰ない
人は生まれて
人は死んでゆく
肉体は滅びるよ
灰の中から蘇るものは情熱
次の世代へ
夢はリンカーネーション
何度でもデジャヴューのような
遠い記憶
まるでリンカーネーション
今もまた
無意識のうちに
どこかへ走ってる
いくつ目の涙で
諦めるのか
いくつ目の命で
叶うものなのか
ご視聴ありがとうございました